{
    "id": "ce14440dc9db42718d172a77e70bc50b",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We moved to the countryside so that our kids would have a garden in ………………….. to play.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "where",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She may have missed her train, …………………. case we ought to wait for her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "in which"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He got married again two months later, …………………. surprised everybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I was impressed by the way …………………. she did it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "in which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house …………………. I was born in.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you think you can give me ………………….. I need?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We have got everything …………………. we ordered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost his cool, ………………… point I left for home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "at which"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We tested hundreds of jackets none of ………………… was completely waterproof.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Come and see us anytime ………………… you are free.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "when",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}